2021. We'll have the invocation by Part G, Mr. Griff-Ginnells.
Heavenly Father, we're thankful for our community and our city leaders who have
asked that you're with them denied as they make decisions that affect us all that you
had gotten. It's in your name with great name. Amen. Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which
we advance one nation under God and invisible with liberty and justice for all.
Before we begin, let's get to personal branches. Five, coin list.
Let's go move.
Check it.
Mm-hmm.
That was the wine.
Do it.
Five, six minutes.
Wait.
Six minutes from the December 4th, 2020.
Are you ready for meeting?
Motion.
Second.
Eight set.
Seven.
You know, Straton Edmunds, a former claim for Jardé
Realizing them out of nine hundred and fifteen dollars.
Mayor Rivers of the Council inside your package.
Tonight you have got a BA in there explaining the following
that this claims went personal services.
Anne Disparsements occurred from October 23rd through November 14th.
On behalf of the city of Miami folks,
I'm reviewing pleading and filings.
Another documentation prepared responses there too.
Anne's been attending with the Miami team.
They need to dance safety issues.
Realizing Straton Edmunds.
They've contaminated sediments, study, transport study,
involvement and circuit court appeals to follow up.
That's well as some coordination and communication
that are trying to help me answer the question you'll have.
With that of our 750,000 budget.
The payment of this claim would result in us having the remaining six
hundred and four thousand one hundred and five and seventy five six.
Make a motion we approve.
It's seven.
I don't want to.
Hi.
Eight.
I'm going to show River 2D modeling.
They amount of $14,829 and 91 cents.
In your packet, you will see a background document showing this is for
professional services incurred from August 19th to 2023 through November 24th.
On behalf of the city of Miami.
This is for the issue River 2D modeling.
It was the primary engineering effort on this period as well as communications
for the city of Miami.
I think that's a good idea.
If this claim were to be paid for the $14,829 and $90 and $90 and since, it would leave us
remaining balance of this fiscal year budget for this claim of $508,325 and $84.
Thank you much, Jim.
Second.
Williams.
Hi.
East End.
Back.
Central.
Hi.
Welcome water resource board, American Rescue Plan Act Grant, and the agreement between
my and especially utility authority, Donald County, and OWRB, for construction of
a new 300,000 gallon elevated water storage tank, and the improvements to disinfection system, and
borderline extension, to loot two dead ends into the system, grant amount not to exceed two million dollars.
So this is the actual grant agreement between us and OWRB, and we've received, so you
need to previously talked about it.
We were awarded it, so this is actually officially signing the documents for our grant.
This is one one in the triangle.
Yes.
Yeah.
So in the last six and eight, you see where we cleared up the streets and we're going to go.
This is going to work again.
On six and nine A and the Gulf of the Triangle, it's where you're 90.
90 and six and nine A.
Right here in just past the annual arena.
We have a water.
We have a well there right now.
We're going to have the water tower to go with the wells.
Is there any match there for us?
Yes, so we're matching it up to you, Mayan, too.
It depends on what the water tower is.
We previously put it out for a bid and it came in for three million.
So to our match being kind, now we actually have money.
We borrowed money to do the water tower, and so we didn't have enough one to come in at three
million.
So we're going to use the money that we've borrowed for the water tower.
We're going to tie it all together, which would be really cool.
So we'll have the water line that goes down.
We need to use the water college farm and down six and nine A.
So we'll have like a T right there.
So water will transfer throughout the city again.
So I know in the past, when we try to take the water tower that's far there out there,
it's the industrial park offline to clean up in different things.
We have really, really low water pressure up there to Buffalo, around two.
Let's see now.
We have a thing that they want to put a advertisement on it.
I haven't asked him that.
So just also feed over a tree road somehow?
Yes.
So if we have enough money, we would like to pour underneath the turn pipe and the puree
housing right there.
So you know, currently we only have one way that goes underneath the weeds out there.
So far, you know, our first project is the bid out to water tower.
And then we'll do the T section and the third part will be if we have to find out about to pour on any
other.
So that'll have two feeds to the puree housing.
Have you already found out how much that would cost?
What does that have to do with that?
How big is it five there now?
There's actually a chase there now.
What you can like, I would suggest that
if it's you can walk every day to hear some horror.
I don't know if less of my could fit,
but we think we can't just breathe in.
But at least you added yourself.
Yeah, we appreciate that.
But what we have, there's actually a concrete chase
that goes underneath there, and there's a water line underneath there.
We've actually had to send employees to the proper gear
on their thing and hatching.
And we need to just for quite some time.
Yes, there.
So anytime there's a water leak on that line,
you know, there goes out there to hear a housing
that the whole water is shut out there.
So I think you're saying Brad would fit.
Oh, I'm pretty agile for a...
Oh, you're bad.
Like, you say we're a whale over there, though.
Are you already on 10?
10?
Yes, up there.
On top of the hill.
Yeah.
Right there on there, right.
So from that whale, does that feed over there, too?
It can.
But it currently feeds back to the Clearwater,
which is a compression center.
So it pumps back there into the Clearwater, and it kicks it out.
Is that 2 million?
Is that a matching grant?
Or is that we get 2 million?
And whatever it costs over that, we have to pay.
How's that work?
Yeah, so that 2 million is like, we have to...
We put up so much, but most of the day, we'll spend as 2 million.
So, I mean, well, that's when you get their 2 million,
that they need for that.
Yeah, I think that's the water tower.
It's a 250 up to 2 million.
Yeah.
So we got a 2 million to get their full 2 million?
Yes.
Yeah.
But it'll be in those 3 projects.
I don't think we'll have any issues getting the 2 million.
And if you know something great,
documents they do refer to the mayor's list,
plus partner.
I'm sorry.
But I want you to bring that.
Thanks.
I want to be too.
So they're giving us 2 million dollars.
So I want to bring that.
Anyone else will pick a shop over there.
We're done.
We only know that you got to get sent to you.
Yeah.
You know, I'm really proud of Tyler the team
for going after this and getting it.
There's a lot of work going to do it.
And we beat out quite a few communities for this.
This money.
So it really was kind of a big deal.
He was on pins and needles there for a while.
They're waiting to announce it.
And they made a big deal.
Yeah.
It's a big spectacle.
And we got it.
And so we kind of rose to the location.
We tried to show you our work.
Thank you.
We actually finished.
We tied.
There's 3 of us that tied to the most points.
So that was big for two because we want to develop six on eight all.
Yes.
We're going to be nearly each for development.
Just in a minute.
Yeah.
Any other questions for Tyler?
Yes.
You just.
No, you need to.
That's pretty well.
I think we'll show you through.
I'll second.
December.
William.
Hi.
Thank you.
Eastern.
Right.
Perfect.
Hi.
Thank you.
Good, you game.
Tan, another new business, which the business is posting this agenda.
Staff reports, trustee community announcements.
The journalist.
So.
Second.
All right.
We step by.
Williams.
Aye.
Mr. Bernhardt.
The other fire.